These aren't Seeno Evils!
They're Haters.
You've done too much to stand out in this world.
This way!
What are Haters?!
Envy and spite created Haters
of you girls from among the Seeno Evils.
They don't have the guts to show
their faces, but they do have madness.
They're strong in groups.
Maybe as strong as a boss.
Run or hide.
They're after you: the "heroes" in the limelight.
We're "heroes"?
Is your cut okay?
Great.
What's your name?
Yoshida Yae.
Yae, huh?
Hide here until the bell rings.
You can't clear the mission if you don't fight.
Well, focus on maintaining the status quo for today.
I have a solution in mind.
But Yae is hurt.
It's my fault she—
Not a problem.
She'll regenerate in as little as ten minutes in her Egg.
Damn, they found us?
Protect the Egg girl until time runs out.
That's your top priority.
Society is built on "report, contact, consult."
Say it out loud and share it!
Our greatest objective is...
Wonder...
Egg...
Priority.
Ai.
Come on, it's time for breakfast.
Yesterday was rough.
Come on. Get up and help out.
Fine.
Ai?
I know!
You want this, too?
Yeah.
I made you omelet rice for lunch.
I know how much you like it.
You did? Yay.
Oh, and I'll make us sukiyaki for dinner.
Why?
What do you mean? You love sukiyaki, don't you?
You only make it on special days.
Do I really?
I guess so.
Ai, would you have a proper talk with Mr. Sawaki today?
He's really concerned about you.
Would you think about the future, at least a little?
How about it?
I'll think about it.
Ai...
I'll think about it!
Okay, okay.
You went to school like that?
Yup. Glistening lips and eyes like a panda.
A panda?
She's here.
She is?
But...
she's skipping.
What's up?
I wonder.
Now she's lashing out.
Huh?
Why's she doing that?
I don't know. Maybe something happened.
I've had a nightmare like this.
It ended horribly.
Let's just watch for a bit.
Congratulations. I see you managed to escape.
Yeah, but what's with those Haters?
Who asked them to treat us like
heroes? We're not doing this for fun.
Regrettably, they can't be reasoned with.
Those who stand out pay for it,
in any time and in any world.
Didn't you say you "had a solution in mind"?
Yes. Look, here it is now.
Thanks.
That case contains things that will support you.
Basically, it's what you call a "power up."
Like what?
Beats me.
I doubt we'll get to use it all the time.
If you've got something that handy, say so sooner!
These are extremely valuable.
We couldn't have you losing them.
That means, "Don't get used to it, idiots."
They're super cute!
You can have them free of charge. One each, of course.
Pendants?
Pomanders, right?
Wow.
So, how do we use them?
First, you hatch them in this world.
Hatch them?
It's not so difficult.
They respond to body heat, so clasp
them in both hands and gently rub them.
Oh, but don't do it here.
Go home and open them when you're alone.
Why?
They require imprinting.
They see whoever meets their gaze first as their parent.
Chant "veni" to call them from their eggs.
"Redi" to return them.
Latin?
I hope my baby's a hottie.
Hey, what types do you think are in them?
We haven't imprinted yet, so we can trade, right?
Wanna swap with me, Neiru?
No.
I hope you get the ugliest helper.
Ai...
Is something wrong?
You seem different.
It's a long story.
I'm leaving now, Ma'am.
Fine.
Veni.
A snake.
Hello?
I'm not sure how to react.
Again?
Don't worry. We've got backup this time.
Veni.
He ate it!
Haters are their favorite food.
Envy and spite are their bread and butter.
Okay, I'm counting on you!
That should solve our Hater problem.
What's wrong?
Yae, why did you kill yourself?
I can see.
See what?
Dead people, strong grudges...
Like The Sixth Sense?
See?! No one will believe me.
There are unbelievably scary things that only I can see.
Sorry. I don't understand.
It's fine.
My friends left because it creeped them out.
My parents and teachers wouldn't believe me.
In fact, they thought I was crazy and put me in a hospital.
But what really scared me was what came next.
What?
That hospital was overflowing
with lots of people's resentment.
It was way worse than ghosts.
Those people's voices and their terrifying faces
poured into my head day in and day out!
Calm down!
Listen, a boss is coming. I'll get ready for it.
It's already here!
Huh?
Good evening, Ohto.
G-Good evening.
It's dinner time, so dry your hair quickly.
Oh, I'll help you.
Oh no, I'm fine.
Please take a seat.
Huh?
He's staying?
Here.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for dinner.
Ai, wait a moment.
Ai!
We have something to tell you.
If it's school, I need a little more—
It's not school. Just sit down.
Listen calmly, okay?
We've been thinking that we'd like to start dating.
Of course, we're not going to do
anything if you're not okay with it.
My uncle and Ai's mom?
That means we might end up being family!
What are you excited about?
Well, I mean...
Right, Ai?
Does she look happy to you?
Are you against it?
I told them to do whatever. It's none of my business.
Well, you fought as hard as you could.
And that I wouldn't take care of them
or live with them in the future.
I said I'd put them in a home and only visit sometimes.
Nice. You really let 'em have it.
Why? Do you feel bad for your real dad?
No. They're already divorced, and
Dad might have someone new himself.
Then, there's no problem—
There is.
Don't you listen to people, Momoe?
You mean that my uncle might have been
involved in Koito's suicide?
I told you, there's no way.
And what if there was?
Mr. Sawaki's younger than Ai's mom.
He'd be her younger live-in boyfriend.
So?
"So"?
Live-in boyfriends are always abusing their girlfriends' kids.
Violently if it's a son, sexually if it’s a daughter.
I'm sorry, but don't lump my uncle
in with the men your mom's dated.
What'd you say?!
You mean it's possible that Mr.
Sawaki likes young girls like us,
meaning that Ai's mom is a decoy and he's really after Ai?
No way. Besides, he knows that Ai's my friend.
I don't think it's like that.
I just... don't like not knowing about Koito.
If they marry, you'll have to cover
for him to protect your mom.
Unbelievable. I've heard enough.
I'm sorry, Momo. That's not what I...
What on Earth are they talking about?
No clue.
Not what clothes would go with
those necklaces, that's for sure.
Sometimes, family matters take
precedence over life-or-death battles.
I guess we'll never know the truth
unless we bring Koito back and ask her.
Occam's razor.
There might be a factor complicating matters.
Huh?
What? There's more?!
Ai likes Mr. Sawaki, too.
Oh! Yeah!
"The simplest theory is the best."
What do you mean, Neiru?!
You're wrong! I don't...
Emotional!
Complicated and emotional!
I don't! That's totally impossible!
Stop!
Stay away!
I didn't ask to be able to see you.
I'm not your friend or anything like that!
No!
No...
Stop it!
It's here?
But I can't...
Please, don't kill that girl!
Prayer beads?
You mean that my uncle might have been
involved in Koito's suicide?
We've been thinking that we'd like to start dating.
There might be a factor complicating matters.
There's no reason to have a complex.
Your eyes are charming.
Ai likes Mr. Sawaki, too.
No.
I don't.
No!
Don't tell me—
I'm telling you, I don't!
Now I'm really mad!
You can see me, Miss?
Yeah. But I can't be your friend.
I bet it was tough,
dealing with these monsters all on your own.
You believe me?
Of course.
Your name is Leon.
Not very creative.
Veni.
Redi.
Ai, Mr. Sawaki is leaving.
Don't mind me.
See you next week, Ohto.
I'm home.
In the bath, Ai?
Welcome back.
Oh, don't leave your dirty clothes here.
What do I always tell you?
Turn the pockets inside-out for washing.
I'll leave what was in your pockets here.
Hey!
Ai?!
You'll catch a—
I'm fine!
Where are you going dressed like that?
School!
Huh?!
Bye-bye, Mr. S.
Goodbye.
Mr. Sawaki.
Ohto?
What's wrong?
Ohto.
The sky is clear and beautiful.
It was a passing shower.
I...
I'm...
going to go to school!
To be continued.